

## Experience

#### CHIEF REBEL, STOCKHOLM

Gameplay Programmer | November 2022 - Ongoing

- At Chief Rebel, I worked as a Gameplay Programmer, utilizing C++ and Blueprints with Epic's Gameplay Ability System (GAS) in Unreal Engine 5.
- When I started my position, I mostly delved into code, implementing a new needed system for the game, and gaining comprehensive insights into Unreal Engine's various components. As the project advanced, I collaborated closely with the designer, primarily working with blueprints and occasionally introducing new blueprint nodes to meet our delivery commitments to the publisher. Most of the time, I focused on the prototype phases, which meant that I also had to work on other parts of the game like characters, UI, and some other systems to make the prototyping work as intended and/or give the designer a quick "feel" of the new system.

#### POSTNORD, MÖLNDAL

Mailman | 2015 - 2020

• I worked at Postnord for a full year between 2015 - 2016 and then every summer during my studies at Blekinge Institute of Technology.

## Education

# BLEKINGE INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, KARLSKRONA



MSc in Game and Software Engineering | 2016 - 2021

- The program contained courses such as: Multivariable Calculus, Linear Algebra, C & C++, Databases (MySQL + Python), Game Physics, OpenGL, DirectX 12, WebGL, SCRUM and Git. The program also contained two 3D game projects:
  - A smaller one built from the ground up with OpenGL: https://gamejolt.com/games/daedalusmaze/404262
  - A bigger one built from the ground up with DirectX 12: https://gamejolt.com/games/Hell\_Loop/578483
- My focus in the thesis centered on Variable Rate Shading within DirectX 12, examining the boundaries of tier 2 without compromising substantial image quality. http://urn.kb.se/resolve?urn=urn:nbn:se:bth-21868

## Profile

I am a positive and driven person who finds it easy to collaborate with others. I think that problem solving in coding is exciting and that it feels very rewarding when you manage to come up with solutions to achieve the goals. Being creative is something I really like and combining that with programming places game creation on the top of my interests. Therefore, I want to be involved where I can contribute to interesting solutions and create entertaining game experiences.

#### Contact information

Name: Fredrik Lind

Address: Per Hiertas Väg 3

Postal number: 141 70 Segeltorp, Stockholm

Mail: f.flind@hotmail.com Phone: +46722515909

Github: https://github.com/fredrix96

LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com/in/fredrik-lind-

50616b5b/

# Language

Swedish, native - Fluent English - Excellent

## Extra merits

Unity

Driver License

#### References

Provided on request